吸血鬼后裔  前请提要  佩内洛普离开学校了
Previously on Legacies... Penelope is leaving the school.
我知道啊
Oh, yeah. I knew that.
你除了自己从没考虑过其他人的感受
You never consider anybody's feelings but your own.
这是萨尔瓦多的学校
It's a log of everything
里面所有记录下来的 一切
written down at the Salvatore School,
我想让你看看你爸爸写的关于
and I want you to read  what your dad wrote
一种叫做融合的东西
about something called  the Merge.
马里之洼是什么
What's Malivore?
是一个地狱的维度
It's a hell dimension
会吞噬所有的生物  并且抹去他们集体良知的
that consumes creatures and wipes their existence
全部存在
from the collective conscience.
我都不知道我在马里之洼多久了
I don't even know how long I was in Malivore.
然后有一天我回到了这里
And then, one day, I found myself back here.
怀孕了
I was pregnant.
所以兰登就是
So Landon is the, uh,
超自然的圣灵感孕说吗
supernatural  immaculate conception?
你隐瞒了我妈的秘密
You are keeping a secret about my mom?
- 我要走了  - 兰登  兰登
- I can't be here right now.-  Landon. Landon!
你的人员没能完成她的营救任务
Your asset failed her retrieval mission.
我清理了她的烂摊子
I cleaned up her mess.
在你把他扔进坑里之前  进行平常的盘问
Usual debrief before you throw him into the pit.
看看他来自哪里  家庭情况
Find out where he's from. Family.
还有没有其他什么他愿意交代的死而复生的人了
Any other phoenixes he's willing to give up.
然后问他那把刀的事情
Then ask him about the knife.
那把刀吗
As in the knife?
我在学校的时候
When I was at the school,
我听说他想偷那把刀
I heard he tried to steal it.
我想知道他为什么想要
And I'd like to know why he wanted
那个坑的其中一把锁
one of the locks to the pit.
应该不会很难的
Shouldn't be too difficult.
他基本都没有反抗就录了那个留言
He recorded the voice mail with minimal resistance.
现在没人看着我们了
No one's watching us now.
听我说
Look,
我已经跟其他人说我什么都不知道了
I already told the other guys I don't know anything.
你可以杀了我  但我是死而复生之人
You can kill me, but I'm part phoenix,
所以我还是会在一阵火焰中重生
so I'm just gonna come back to life
这些灰烬可是会很难收拾的
in a burst of flames, and there's gonna be a lot of ash
而且等我回来之后
to clean up. And after I come back,
我也还是什么都不知道
I'm not gonna know anything.
我不是来审问你的  兰登
I'm not here to interrogate you, Landon.
其实  我来
In fact, I'm here
是可以给你一些答案的
so you can finally get some answers.
当他们创造了马里之洼的锁
When they created the locks to Malivore,
同时也做了圈套
they also created decoys
所以就没有人知道哪神器是真的
so no one would know which three artifacts were the real thing.
我觉得或许你可以帮助我
I think you might be able to help me with that.
其中一个神器在呼唤你对吧
Is one of these artifacts calling to you?
低语一样
Like a whisper,
一种痒
an itch?
第一  我没什么感觉
A) I don't feel anything.
第二  就算我有  我也不会帮助
And B) even if I did, I'm not helping
绑架我的人
the people who kidnapped me.
这跟三元素没关系
Oh, this isn't for Triad.
他们想要这些神器继续隐藏的
No, they want these artifacts to stay hidden.
说实话
To be clear,
是我想把它们都扔进坑里
I want to toss them into the pit
然后打开马里之洼大门
and unlock Malivore.
谢谢你的坦诚
Thanks for being honest.
真好啊
That's refreshing.
但我真的不会帮助你的
But now I'm really not going to help you.
我跟你讲个故事
I'll tell you a story.
听完之后  你再来决定你要不要
And at the end of it, you can decide whether you want
- 帮助我吧  - 你觉得一个故事
- to help me or not. - You think a story
- 就能改变我的想法吗  - 这个故事会的
- is gonna change my mind? - This one will.
因为这是你父亲的故事
Because it's the story of your father.
* Ask me no questions *
吸血鬼后裔
第一季   第十五集
* I will tell you no lies *
* Careful what you wish for *
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
* We're looking for angels in the darkest of skies *
* Saying that we wanted more *
* I feel like I'm falling *
* But I'm trying to fly *
* Where does all the good go? *
* We're looking for answers in the highest of highs *
翻 译  岛岛
* But will we ever, ever know? *
* If you feel it, could you let me know? *
翻 译  RossyGeng
* Oh... * * If you feel it, could you let me know? *
翻 译  kkarlieygi
* Oh... * * I'm not asking *
* For a miracle *
翻 译  Monica
* Ask for forever when the end is in sight *
* Showing what you want to *
* And I need *
* You to know *
* I'm not asking for a miracle *
翻 译  岛岛
* But if love is enough *
* Could you let it show? *
* If you feel it, could you let me know? *
校 对   岛岛
注意啊
Heads up!
特 效   麦 斯
* If you asking for a miracle. *
差点把你头打掉
That almost took your head off.
我来这里多久了
Yo, how long have I been here?
一小时了  而且你移动的就跟
For an hour. But you've been going through the motions
僵尸一样
like a zombie.
你确定你没事吗
You sure you're okay?
我没事  还有
Yeah, I'm fine. And, look,
你不用因为我是你老大  就假装
you don't need to pretend like you give a crap about me
很在乎我的样子
just 'cause I'm your alpha.
比赛继续  开始吧
The game's back on. Come on.
里克  抱歉这么离开了
Hey, Ric. Sorry to take off like that,
但我需要点时间
but I just needed a little time.
所以我要去露营一段时间
So I'm going camping for a while.
希望我之后能跟上课业
Hopefully I can catch up on classwork later.
替我跟 拉斐尔和杰德问好
Tell Raf and Jed hi for me.
杰德
Jed?
为什么要跟杰德问好
Why would he say hi to Jed?
你应该去找他
You should go after him.
感觉哪里不对
Something doesn't make sense.
霍普  三元素已经抓过他一次了
Hope... Triad already tried to come
- 他自己在外面不安全  - 我们瞒了他
- for him once. It's not safe for him out there. - We kept
■
看最新热播美剧
上人人视频app
可在线观看 离线缓存
各大应用市场
及AppStore皆可下载
扫描即刻下载
很多秘密  我觉得他需要一点时间
a massive secret from him, and I think he just needs some time
来消化  我觉得我们应该尊重他的隐私
to process that. I think we should respect
等待就好了
his privacy and just wait.
我知道这个表情
I know that look.
怎么了
What's wrong?
这些孩子最近经历太多了
These kids have been through so much lately.
我已经尽我所能帮助 拉斐尔了
I've done all I can to help Rafael,
但是霍普药水的影响更加严重了
but the side effects of Hope's elixir are getting worse.
他快没时间了
He's losing time,
有各种攻击性的片段
having flashes of aggression.
我觉得他还是在他的狼人思维和
I think he's still sliding between his wolf mind
人类思维中切换
and his human mind.
我会对盯着他的
I will-- I'll keep an eye on him.
你过去这几周忙的都要冒烟了
You've been running on fumes these past few weeks.
找人来帮帮忙也不是坏事啊
It wouldn't hurt to bring in someone else to help,
甚至可以帮助研究拉斐尔的病情
maybe even assist in researching Rafael's condition.
多利安太骄傲了不会回来的
Dorian is too proud to come back.
- 你知道的  - 你也知道
- You know that. - And you know
我很尊重你的
how much I respect you.
但你确定问题是他的自尊吗
But are you sure it's his pride that's the problem?
这里是被怪物袭击了吗
Was there a monster attack in here?
你来了啊
There you are.
我等的烦死了  所以我
I got tired of waiting, so I attempted
所以我自己试着做了一个香蕉奶油派
a banana cream pie by myself.
在哪里啊
Where is it?
垃圾桶  我都说了是尝试
In the garbage. I said "attempted."
所以还是回到第一计划吧
So we're gonna go back to plan A,
你要给我做一个
and you are gonna make it for me.
跟你更新一下  乔西昨晚没回来
Status update: Josie didn't come back last night.
我觉得她睡在佩内洛普以前的房间里了
I think she slept in Penelope's old room,
这样很容易感染乙肝的好不好
which is a really good way to get hepatitis B.
你有睡觉吗  你感觉有点
Have you slept at all? You seem a little...
专注  有动力  一针见血吗
Focused? Motivated? On point?
- 好的吧  - 不在同一间屋子里睡觉就意味着
- Sure. Yeah. - Not sleeping in the same bedroom means
双胞胎原谅抱抱没戏了
that Twin Forgiveness Cuddle is off the table.
但她都在图书馆待着
But she's been holed up in the library,
所以给她一点零食应该就好了吧
so a snack offering should do the trick.
你知道  早晚你得要道歉的
At some point, you might actually have to apologize.
永远不能道歉
Never apologize.
相信我
Okay. Trust me, okay?
我们就这样  我自私
This is what we do. I'm selfish,
她生闷气
then she sulks,
然后我给她好吃的
and then I offer baked goods.
- 别人帮你做的好吃的  - 这让你
- Someone else's baked goods. - It's giving you
也有点事情干了吗不是
something to do with yourself, isn't it?
该你更新近况了
Your turn for an update.
我们
Any word
傻呵呵的精灵有没有找你啊
from our mop-headed elf?
他说他需要时间思考
He says he needs time to think.
我也不知道  我感觉如果我
Hmm. I don't know. I feel like if I could
知道应该说什么  他就会回来了
figure out the right thing to say, then he'd come back.
那就练习啊
So, practice.
艾玛有一个棱镜
Emma has this prism
可以引发对话
that simulates a conversation.
之前我不在状态的时候
She makes me use it
她会让我用这个跟我爸妈讲话
to talk to my mom and my dad when I'm in a state.
我拿棱镜跟你换
I'll trade you one prism
一个香蕉奶油派
for a banana cream pie.
我给你带了好吃的哦
I brought you some brain food.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
都是你最喜欢的
It's all your favorite things.
你还是问了别人才知道的吧
Which I'm sure somebody else had to tell you.
无意冒犯  但你说什么我都不信
No offense, but I'm not gonna  believe anything you say.
你的操纵人技术绝对顶尖  哥们
I mean, A-plus for manipulation, man.
这个真的很吓人  但是
This is really frightening stuff, but...
这是哪里来的
Where did you get this?
- 这跟我接下来要讲的东西有关 - 不用了
- It's all part of what I'm about to tell you. - Look,
我已经知道我爸了
I already know about my dad.
我妈被马里之洼的一个怪物搞怀孕了
My mom got pregnant by one of the monsters in Malivore.
那么
Well,
那就更容易讲我的故事了
then he'll be easy to spot in my story.
大概一千年以前
Around a millennia ago,
在世界的某一处  有很多怪物
in certain parts of the world, there were monsters.
在其中一个地区
And in one region...
没有什么比龙要更加吓人
...there was no monster  more terrifying
的怪物了
than dragons.
就他们自己而言  没有任何派别
On their own, no faction was any match
能与龙匹敌
for dragons.
所以他们成立了一个邪恶的联盟
So an unholy alliance  was formed.
一个女巫
A witch,
一个狼人  一个吸血鬼
a werewolf and a vampire...
走进了一个酒吧  这个笑话我听说过哦
Walked into a bar. I think I've heard this one before.
抱歉
Sorry.
三元素融合了他们的血液
The Triad combined their blood,
加上黑魔法
using black magic
创造一个能够吃掉龙的傀儡
to create a golem capable of consuming the dragons.
他们给这个生物下了咒  让其贪得无厌   永远吃不饱
They spelled the creature  to have an insatiable hunger.
但这个咒语也让他无法伤害女巫  狼人
But their spell also made it  unable to harm witches,
或者吸血鬼
werewolves, or vampires.
他们叫它为黑暗吞噬者
They named it Eater of the Dark.
当那些化成人形
When the dragons,
的龙回到了他们袭击过的村庄
in human form, returned  to collect the treasure
收敛财富的时候
from all the villages  they had attacked,
它在等着他们
it was waiting for them.
抓住了他们
It took them,
吃掉了他们
consumed them.
令他们惊讶是
To their surprise,
这个生物比他们想象中还要强大
the creature was more effective  than they could have dreamed.
龙消失了之后
After the dragons were gone,
它见到其他任何怪物就吃
it kept eating every monster  it could,
把它们吞进自己无限的身体里
swallowing them into an endless space inside itself.
你是说那个泥人吃了我爸
You're saying that the golem ate my dad?
不  兰登
No, Landon.
那个泥人就是你爸
Your father is the golem.
黑暗吞噬者
The Eater of the Dark.
- 嗨  - 嗨
Hi. Hi.
别客气
Knock yourself out.
第一回会有点奇怪
The first time's kind of freaky,
因为你几乎是在和自己的潜意识交流
because you're basically talking to your subconscious.
谢谢  这个给你
Thanks. This is for you.
双胞女巫史
我看你爸在读这本  一直锁在
I saw your dad reading it. He keeps it
办公室的柜子里  所以里面肯定
locked up in his office, so it's bound to have something
有乔西在找的关于吞噬的内容
about that Merge thing Josie's looking for.
这一回你和我爸的特殊关系
For once, your weird relationship with my dad
终于派上用场了
actually comes in handy.
是啊  小心点
Right. Uh, just be careful.
如果你爸是在隐瞒什么
If your dad's hiding something,
我相信是有原因的
I'm sure it's for a good reason.
无论是什么  我都可以处理好的
I'm sure I can handle it, whatever it is.
我有预感一切都会没事的
I just have this feeling that everything is gonna work out just fine.
你能感觉到吗  好像整个学校都在振动
Can you feel it? It's like the whole school is vibrating.
咱们都要找回自己的人
We're both gonna get our people back.
你好啊
Hey there.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
挺好
Yeah.
我很抱歉
Yeah. Sorry.
这是我第一次和魔法幻象交流
this is my first time talking to a magical hologram.
幻象
Hologram?
你什么意思  幻象  什么意思
What do you mean, a hologram? What does that mean?
我是假的吗  你在说什么呢
That I'm not real? What are you talking about?
天啊  求你别这样
Oh, my God, don't do that.
抱歉
Sorry. Yeah.
就是看你挺紧张的  我想缓解尴尬的气氛
You just seemed tense. I was trying to break the ice.
好吧  至少我知道这个幻象真的很像你
Well, at least I know this is a pretty accurate version of you.
这点你挺感谢自己的吧
You can thank yourself for that, I guess.
你有什么想和我说的吗
You had something you wanted to say to me?
是啊
Yeah. Um...
我应该早点把你妈妈和所有事
I should have told you about your mom
都告诉你的
and-and the whole thing earlier.
我一直想保护你不受伤害
I mean, I was just trying to protect you from being hurt.
所以我就想说
So I just wanted to say
如果害你伤心了我很抱歉
that I'm sorry if I hurt you.
就这些吗
What, that's it?
你在因为伤我心
You're "sorry if
觉得抱歉
I hurt you"?
- 是的  - 好吧  如果
- I am. - Okay, then I
你真心道歉的话  那我接受
accept your apology if you're actually sorry.
- 你怎么回事  - 你真的认为
- What's your problem? - I mean, do you
说这一番话对我有用吗
seriously think that speech would have worked on me?
拜托  这不是你
I mean, come on, that's not what you
- 真正想表达的  - 你怎么知道
- actually wanted to say. - How would you know?
因为我就是你的映射啊  忘了吗
Because I am you, remember?
好吧
Fine.
那你告诉我  我想说什么  我就说
Then you tell me what it is that I want to say, and I'll say it.
不是这样的  霍普  你要倾听
That's not how this works, Hope. You have to listen.
倾听什么
Listen to what?
即使是幻象的你也这么烦人
Even fake you is infuriating.
天哪
God!
那么个泥人傀儡
How can something that's basically
怎么能是我爸呢
a mud robot be my father?
因为它不会一直都是泥人
Because it didn't stay a golem.
在吸收了所有怪物的DNA之后
With each monster's DNA it absorbed...
它进化了
it evolved.
最终  变得有意识
Eventually, it became sentient...
有感情
aware.
他真正的活过
He was truly alive.
等那里的怪物都被消灭后
And when the region was cleared of all the monsters,
三元素想让它变回泥土
the Triad wanted to return him back to mud.
因为是他们创造了他
Since they were the ones who created him,
也只有他们才能毁掉他
only they could destroy him.
他们只需要清除
All they needed to do  was wipe away the symbol
他额头上的标志
on his forehead.
但他背叛了自己的创造者
But he betrayed his creators.
和当初救过的人类达成了交易
He made a deal with all the humans he'd saved.
人们不允许他们的新神
They could not let  their new god
就这么消失
be taken from them.
便放他自由徘徊  让他继续吞噬怪物
The humans set him free to wander the earth and continue consuming,
所有关于怪物的记忆都消失了
erasing all memory that the monsters ever existed.
但随着时间变化
But over time...
就像伊甸园中亚当和夏娃一样
like Adam  in the Garden of Eden,
他意识到自己的孤单
he realized he was alone.
他最终做了所有生物都会做的事
So he did what all creations  eventually do.
创造
Create.
他装饰了那些像他一样的人
He fashioned beings like him.
他的孩子们
His children.
- 他的血脉可以  - 得了吧
- A lineage that could... - Man...
这段之前说得真好
You were doing so good up until that part.
按你说的剧情走向  我差点就信了
I was almost into it, as far as origin stories go,
但你却要我相信自己是
but you're asking me to believe that I'm
是有记忆的神奇泥人
a magical mud man with implanted memories.
恰恰相反
Quite the opposite.
你知道
You see...
他创造的所有孩子都不完美
all the children he fashioned were imperfect.
有瑕疵  没有人拥有这样的能力
Flawed. None of them had his powers.
他们都很脆弱  不能生育
All of them had weaknesses and all were sterile,
无法延续他的传奇
unable to reproduce and continue his legacy.
他是种族唯一的一人
He was created to be the only one of his kind.
从没打算能成为一个种族
He was never intended to be a species
或者有自己的血脉
or have a bloodline of his own.
但是
But...
他发现了生理繁殖的方法
he found a way to reproduce biologically.
生个半人类的儿子
To have a son who was part human.
这孩子完美无缺
A son who was perfect.
可以永生
A son who could live forever
可以血脉不息
and continue the species.
你是他毕生努力创造的产物
You are what he's been trying to create his entire life.
我一直很含蓄
I was trying to be all coy.
给你  这是爸书房里的神秘书  我知道你一直在找
Here. It's a secret book from Dad's study-- I know you're looking into
关于融合什么的
this Merge crap,
我只是想帮你  换取点信任
so I just want a little credit for helping.
你有想过或许我不用你的帮助
Did you stop to think that maybe I didn't want your help,
或许我想靠我自己
that maybe I wanted something,
去搞定这些事吗
anything that was entirely my own?
是因为分房间的事吗
Is this about having separate rooms?
没事的  睡佩内洛普的就好了
That's fine, okay? Just take Penelope's.
你还是不明白吗
You seriously still don't get it.
这不是房间的事
This isn't about needing space.
是我人生的每个脆弱时刻
This is about every waking moment of my life
都被你压制着
being suffocated by you.
我们不仅要有自己的房间
We shouldn't just have our own rooms.
我们还应该有自己的人生
We should have our own lives.
我们应该做自己
We should be our own people.
我分享了我撒过的谎
You know, I've told  my fair share of lies,
撒得最好的谎是让人快要相信的
and the best lie is one that someone already wants to believe.
你想让我相信
And you're asking me to believe that
我找了好多年的父亲
the father that I've been looking for for years
也一直在搜寻我
has actually been searching for me?
我为什么要信你
Why should I believe you?
因为当时我也在
Because I was there.
几年以后  他对孩子的企图
Over the years, his attempts at children
变得更加精细
became more refined,
与人类一般无二
indistinguishable from humans.
我们的父亲是个有天赋的艺术家
Our father is a very gifted artist.
我们的父亲
Our father?
是的
Yes...
弟弟
little brother.
我说了
Like I said...
当时我也在
...I was there.
呼吸  冷静
Breathe. Stay calm.
不  不  别这样
No, no, don't do this.
你还好吗
Hey, are you okay?
后退
Stay back.
没事  会好的
It's fine. It'll pass.
我们该怎么办
Just... What do we do? Do we need
- 用去树林里嚎几嗓子吗  - 不用
- to do the yelling- in-the-woods thing? No,
我就想知道这个融合是什么东西
I just, I need to find out what this Merge thing is, okay?
感觉像是个咒语
I feel like it's a spell
她会用来离开
that she's gonna use to just leave
或者解散我们什么的
or break us up or something!
好了  深呼吸  深呼吸
All right, deep breaths. Deep breaths.
我给芙蕾雅姑妈打电话  她会知道融合的事的
I'll call my Aunt Freya-- she'll know something about the Merge.
- 好吗  - 好的
- Okay? - Okay.
好的
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
你不是应该和新朋友玩的吗
Shouldn't you be hanging out with your new best friend?
所以我才来这的
Oh, that's actually why I'm here.
我觉得要出事
I-I think some sort of crash is brewing.
那你就躲离远点
Then you should stay away.
我知道你生她的气
Um, look, I know that you're mad at her,
但她毕竟是你姐
but... she's still your sister,
- 她真的需要你的帮助  - 为何
- and she really needs your help. - Why?
这是她自找的
She did this to herself.
怎么会  她控制不住她的大脑
What? She can't control her brain chemistry.
她可以吃药啊
She can choose to take her medication.
自从我们见过她妈之后她就没有吃过药
She hasn't taken it since we saw her mom, because she doesn't like
因为她不喜欢药物带来的感觉
the way that it makes her feel.
所以她试了魔法手镯
So she tried magical bracelets
释放她的糟心事
and releasing her inner bitch
然后用神秘瀑布镇小姐的事来分心
and then distracting herself with Miss Mystic Falls,
但该来的总会来
but all of that is just delaying the inevitable.
让她完蛋是唯一能
Letting her crash is the only way
改变一切的办法
anything will ever change.
看着点  狼仔
Watch it, wolf.
你叫我什么
What'd you say to me?
我说  看着点
I said, watch it...
狼仔
wolf.
带你的吸血鬼们
Get your vampires
- 快滚  - 嘿
- out of my face. - Hey, hey, hey!
住手
Stand down.
别碰我
Get off of me!
狼人们  住手
Hey! Hey, wolves, stand down!
快点
Now!
够了
Enough!
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman.
都回班级去
Everyone back to class.
请让一下
Clear the way, please.
- 我很抱歉  - 过来
- I'm sorry. EMMA: Coming through.
- 霍普  怎么了  - 别装作
- Hey, Hope. What's going on? - Don't pretend like
- 不记得我们上次谈话的样子  - 我就是觉得
- you don't remember our last conversation. - I just figured
你想要重新开始
you'd want a fresh start.
看来我的潜意识也会出错啊
Oh. Guess even my subconscious can get stuff wrong.
说得好
Touché.
你知道自己想说什么了吗
So, did you figure out what you wanted to say yet?
是啊  知道了
Uh, yeah, actually, I did.
我想说的是  我一直保护你
And what I wanted to say is this: I have been protecting you
从你来这我就视你的安全为第一位
and putting your safety first ever since you got here.
那我该拿秘密怎么办
So what was I supposed to do with this secret? Hmm?
不保护你了吗
Just stop protecting you?
■
看最新热播美剧
上人人视频app
可在线观看 离线缓存
各大应用市场
及AppStore皆可下载
扫描即刻下载
我知道孤儿是什么感觉
I know exactly what it feels like to be an orphan.
我在努力不让你有孤儿的感觉  这样你就能生我气了
Okay? I was saving you from that. So you can be mad
- 但我这样做是因为我在乎你  - 不是
- at me, but I was doing it because I care about you. - No.
你这么做是为了不让我离开
You were doing it because you didn't want me to leave.
因为你害怕被抛弃的感觉  就像你妈离开了你
Because you fear being abandoned, like how your mom left
你爸也离开了  所以你才逃离
and your dad left-- it's why you run.
这和我父母无关
This has nothing to do with my parents.
那当你穿上你爸给你挑的裙子的时候
Then why did you start crying
为什么哭了呢
when you wore a dress your dad picked out?
我们结束了
Whoa. We're done.
霍普  你根本没在听我说
Hope, you're not listening.
我父亲在我身上看到了他自己
My father saw himself in me.
我假装自己不是土
I was clay pretending to be something it wasn't.
他因此看不起我
He despised me for it.
他抛弃了我  就像之前所有的失败者一样
He threw me away like all the other failures who came before.
我知道那是什么感觉
I know what that's like.
那你就能理解我为什么会背叛他
Then you'll understand why I betrayed him.
我们的父亲尽他所能的吸食一切生物
Our father consumed  every creature he could.
他的供应物没了  他就会变得虚弱
And when his supply ran out,  he grew weak...
易被攻击
vulnerable.
那时人类回来了
And that's when  the humans came back.
他最初的崇拜者的后代
The descendants  of his original worshippers,
一个秘密的群体
a secret society.
我告诉他们
I told them
他试图创造一个家族
of his attempts  to create a lineage,
告诉他们他是如何违背自然的  试图孕育一个新物种
how he was violating nature,  trying to birth a new species.
我带他们找到了他
I led them to him.
他们做了人类该做的事
And they did what humans do.
他们背叛了他们的神
They rebelled  against their god.
他们付钱给女巫  让她们用黑魔法诱捕他
They paid witches who used  black magic to trap him...
然后溶解他
...and dissolve him,
把他变回原始状态
returning him  to his natural state.
一个黑色的坑
The black pit.
有怪物所在的无尽的黑暗
The endless darkness where the monsters are.
这不只是个地方
It's not just a place.
这是我们父亲的遗骨
It's what remains of our father.
黑暗吞噬者
The Eater of the Dark.
- 他的名字是  - 马里之洼
- His name is...   - Malivore.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
你相信你自己吗
Would you believe you?
可能不吧
Probably not.
那再说一次
Then again,
我从来不会在不知道为什么要偷神器的情况下
I've never stolen an artifact without even knowing
偷过神器
why I did it.
那把刀和骨灰瓮都是
The knife and the urn were both part
溶解他的咒语的组成
of the spell that dissolved him.
- 但因为他是永生的  - 没什么是永生的
- But since he was immortal...  - Nothing's immortal.
总是有漏洞的  大自然创造了一种平衡
There's always a loophole. Nature creates a balance.
这是魔法史导论里说的
That's Intro to Magical History.
我已经看了差不多一周了
I've been taking it for, like, a week.
很好
Very good.
但在找到那个漏洞之前
But until that loophole could be found,
他们用了三个封印把他锁了起来
they bound him with three locks.
创造了三个诱饵
Created three decoys.
只能由马里之洼的血解封
It can only be unlocked by Malivore's blood,
所以他们把那些东西藏得很远
so they hid them far away.
我已经能找到
I've been able
最后四个神器的位置了
to track down where the last four artifacts are.
现在我需要你告诉我哪个是真的封印
Now I need you to tell me which is the real lock
这样我们就能把他放出来了
so we can set him free.
事情本来可能已经失控了
This could have gotten out of hand.
对  但没有
Yeah, but... it didn't.
而且拉斐也道歉了
And Raf apologized.
你真是个好人  里克
You're a good man, Ric.
但你是人类
But you're human.
这些孩子要多久才能明白
How long until these kids figure out
你对这所学校的控制其实是假象
that the control you have of this school is an illusion?
在你无法阻止的打斗之前吗
Before there's a fight you cannot stop?
我终于知道我能帮到什么了
I finally realized what I can do to help.
我正在休假
I'm taking a sabbatical.
但
But...
但这能帮到什么吗
but how is that supposed to help?
我希望这会是一个警钟
I'm hoping it'll be a wake-up call.
这所学校的使命越来越大
The mission of this school has grown.
当事情遭到你最终不得不承认的时候
And I don't want to be here
我不想还在这里
when it gets bad enough for you to finally admit that.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我来拿些东西
I came to get some stuff,
但我还是等会再来吧
but I guess I'll come back later.
不用  没事
No, it's fine.
随便拿吧
Take whatever you need.
不用担心我
Don't worry about me.
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
我所做的一切
All I've ever done
都是担心你
is worry about you.
又来  又是
Oh, here we go. The whole
“我受够了丽兹的阴影”演讲吗
"I'm tired of being in Lizzie's shadow" speech?
你猜怎么着  相互依赖需要两个人
Well, guess what. Codependency takes two people.
没错  我是很糟糕  很需要帮助
Yes, I'm awful and needy,
但在内心深处  你很乐意躲起来
but deep down, you're happy to hide
然后让我成为他们讨厌的人
and let me be the one that they hate
因为你害怕做自己
because you're too scared to be yourself.
你和我一样都是这个循环的一部分
You are as much a part of this cycle as I am.
你心情不好  等你求我原谅你的手
You're upset. I'll come back
我会回来的
for the part where you beg me to forgive you.
（咒语）
Descanto!  Reboundus!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你需要睡一会
You need to get some help.
别假装你关心我了
Don't pretend that you care about me.
我没有
I don't.
我关心狼群
I care about the pack.
他们会跟着他们的头狼
They follow their alpha.
有个无法控制自己的头狼
And having an alpha who can't control himself
意味着整个狼群都会受伤
means the pack gets hurt.
听着
Look,
作为一个领导者  我是个混蛋
I was a dick as a leader.
所以从那些失去了你所拥有的人那里得到它
So take it from someone who lost what you have.
狼群就是一切
The pack is everything.
如果你关心他们
If you care about them,
你不要让你的自尊心像我一样妨碍你
you won't let your pride get in the way like I did.
我要跟你谈谈拉斐
I need to talk to you about Raf.
我先说
I have to say something first.
弗雷娅刚解释了融合的事
Freya just explained the Merge.
乔西已经猜到了
Josie's pretty much figured it out,
丽兹已经开始有反应了
and, uh, Lizzie is spiraling.
要么你来  要么我来
So, either you do it or I will,
但是时候告诉他们真相了
but it's time to tell them the truth.
如果你是那个背叛他的人
If you're the one who betrayed him,
那为什么现在想放他出来呢
why are you trying to set him free now?
因为我选了错的一边
Because I chose the wrong side.
这个坑和马里之洼的性质相同
The pit had the same properties  as Malivore.
把怪物扔进去  它的记忆会被抹去了
Throw a monster in, its memory  was erased from existence.
这些年间  这个秘密的群体
Within a few years,  the secret society
发展成了一门生意
grew into a business.
三元素公司
Triad Industries.
保护这个世界不受
Keeping the world safe from all the things
所有晚上撞见的东西的伤害
that go bump in the night.
就是清理怪物
It's monster cleaning.
最终  权力使他们堕落
Eventually,  the power corrupted them.
怪物们变成他们不喜欢的样子
Monsters became  whoever they didn't like.
他们想成为的样子被遗忘
Whoever they wanted  to be forgotten.
我以为报复我父亲会让我开心
I thought revenge on my father  would feel sweeter,
但并没有
but it didn't.
所以我就回到他那里去了
So I returned myself to him.
我知道我必须做正确的事
I knew  I had to make things right.
在马里之洼里
Inside Malivore,
只有黑暗
there was only darkness.
我喊  我尖叫
I yelled, I screamed,
但他都不会回应我
but he would not answer me.
他就让我坐在寂静中  惩罚我直到
He let me sit in silence,  punishing me until...
几十年后
decades later,
他突然把我吐了出来
when suddenly he spit me out.
我不知道为什么
I didn't know why
知道我发现了你的照片
till I found that picture of you.
我看到一段视频
And I saw a video of a knife
里面有一把刀  只能用马里之洼的血打开
that could only be unlocked by Malivore's blood.
然后我听到了
And I heard story
一个从坑里出来的孕妇的故事
of a woman who had emerged from the pit pregnant.
随着越来愈多的人类被扔进去
As more humans were thrown in,
他吸收了足够的基因物质
he absorbed enough of their genetic material
能够繁衍
to be able to reproduce.
当三元素出卖了你的母亲
When Triad betrayed your mother,
我们的父亲怜悯她并送她回来的时候
our father had mercy on her and sent her back...
她怀了你
carrying you.
他送我回来找你
He sent me back to find you
因为只有你才是他的血脉
because only you are blood of his blood.
而只有你
And only you
才能让他自由
can set him free.
* Girl *
* Perfectly her... *
有件事我必须让你们俩知道
There's something you both need to know.
* Broken and hurt *
* Soft and asleep in the morning gray *
* Shake off the night and don't hide your face *
* The sun lights the world 8
* With a single flame *
* I want you to see this... *
我之前说的想保护你的话
What I said before about wanting to protect you,
是真的
that was true.
但
But...
我也不想让你走
I also didn't want you to go.
* So run... *
没错  你知道的
And, yeah, you know what,
我讨厌有人离开的时候
I hate it when people leave.
我讨厌
I hate it.
我觉得已经摆脱了失去父母的痛苦
I thought I was over losing my parents,
但我不知道  在过去那几天之后
but I don't know, after the last couple of days
在看到你
and-and after seeing you
躺在树林里
lying there in the woods,
以为你死了之后
thinking that you were dead...
* And uncover your eyes *
* We'll make our escape... *
每次我失去一个人的时候
Every time I lose someone,
我脑海中有个声音
this, uh, voice in my head,
它一直告诉我  都是你的错
it tells me, "It's your fault."
* I need you to see this... *
说我甚至不应该存在
That I shouldn't even technically exist.
说我就是宇宙的错误
That I'm a cosmic mistake.
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
我可能只是想让某个人
I guess I just wanted someone to think
认为我值得留下来
that I'm worth staying for.
很抱歉骗了你  兰登
I'm sorry for lying to you, Landon.
我想让你留下因为我爱你
I wanted you to stay because I love you.
你该不是就想说最后这句吧
You didn't mean to say that last part, did you?
不是
No. Whoa!
你第一次说你爱我的时候
The first time you tell me you love me,
那甚至都不是真正的我
and it's not even the real me?
- 我那是即兴表演  - 什么
- I'm kind of winging it here.  - What?
得了吧
Come on, man.
* You'll come to learn... *
他对这些会怎么反应
H-How would he react to all that, really?
那是他的反应
I mean, that was how he'd react.
他会说些调皮可爱的话
You know, he'd say something roguishly charming
来转移你让他感觉多么脆弱的话题
to deflect from how vulnerable you made him feel,
然后
and then...
他会亲你
well, he'd kiss you.
* My favorite part... *
可能吧
Probably.
所以我们俩中有一人要杀死对方
So, one of us is gonna have to kill the other one?
* My orchid has died... *
更像是吸收
More like absorb.
当双子长到22岁的时候
When Gemini twins turn 22,
融合会决定谁来领导女巫团
the Merge will determine who will lead the coven.
只有一个人能活下来
And only one will survive.
所以你们的母亲一直全球各地跑
That's why your mother's always traveling the globe.
尝试找到解决办法
Trying to find a solution.
但如果双子的女巫团没人了
But if there's no one left from the Gemini coven...
不  比那更深入
No, it goes deeper than that.
这是个诅咒是吗
It's a curse, right?
是对双子双胞胎的诅咒吗
A curse on the Gemini twins?
* Ooh, ooh, I'm sorry... *
是的
Uh, yes.
我知道我应该早点告诉你们
I know I should have told you sooner.
我只是不知道什么时候开口
I just didn't know when.
* That I can't *
该在什么时候
When do you...
告诉你孩子这么残酷的事情才合适呢
tell your children something like that?
* But in the morning... *
你们6岁大时能接受这种事情嘛
I mean, could you handle that news at six?
11岁呢
11?
要告诉自己孩子
When exactly is the right time
自己无力保护她们
to tell your children that you...
我应该找个怎样合适的时间才能告诉你们
that you don't know if you'll be able to protect them?
有时候
I mean, when I...
有时候我看着你们  还觉得你们是小孩子
when I look at you sometimes, I still see you as little girls.
第一次骑自行车
Riding your bikes for the first time.
蹒跚学步的时候
Learning to walk.
踩在我脚上跳舞的时候
Dancing on my feet.
看着你们
When I look at you,
就想起了曾经一切
I see all of that.
所以我一直准备好告诉你们
So I was never ready to tell you.
* Song for you... *
到现在也没准备好
I'm still not.
* Song for you. *
怎么不说话
You're quiet.
我在等
I'm waiting.
真心的吗  都经历了这么多事
Seriously? After all that? Mm-hmm.
我还能对你说什么
I mean, wha-what else could I possibly have to say?
你一整天都在试图说服自己
What you've been trying to tell yourself all day.
是因为你的脑子里太多杂音
But there was too much noise in your head,
所以你才没听到
so you couldn't hear it.
霍普  我有麻烦了
I'm in trouble, Hope.
- 什么  - 你知道这是真的
What? - You already know that's true.
我怎么可能忘带日记  或任何野营装备就进树林
I mean, I went into the woods, but I didn't take my journal?
就跑进树林
Or any camping gear.
我给你留言说了有什么不对劲
I left clues in the voice mail that something wasn't right.
我称萨尔茨曼博士为里克
I called Dr. Saltzman "Ric."
- 我永远不会这么做的  - 你还跟杰德打招呼了
I would never do that. - You said hi to... Jed.
上次我跟杰德打招呼  他把我打得屁滚尿流
Last time I said hey to Jed, he beat the crap out of me.
- 我只是想告诉你有些事不对劲  - 发生了什么事
- I was trying to tell you that something wasn't right. - What happened?
霍普
Hope...
我最后再说一遍  用心倾听
for the last time, just listen.
里克  抱歉我就这样匆匆离开
Hey, Ric, sorry to take off like that,
但我只是需要点时间
but I just needed a little time,
我要出去露营一会儿
so I'm going camping for a while.
我听到了
I can hear...
希望我能赶上功课吧
Hopefully, I can catch up on classwork later.
鞋放在瓷砖地板上的声音
...shoes on a tile floor.
空调开着的声音
An air conditioner running.
替我向拉斐和杰德问好
Tell Raf and Jed hi for me.
房卡刷卡的声音
Keycards being swiped.
三元素
Triad.
肯定是他们干的
I mean, it has to be them.
他们已经来找过他一次了
They've already tried to come for him once.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我要化身神奇女侠了  就这样
I'm gonna go full Wonder Woman, that's what.
- 需要我帮忙吗  - 不用
Do you need any help? No.
我已经有超棒的队友了
I've already got my Super Squad.
但还是谢谢你所做的一切
But thank you for everything.
嘿
Hey, uh...
里克说我应该回去出外勤
Ric said I should probably head back out into the field,
我之前其实是来找你道别的
and I was actually coming to find you and say goodbye
但然后我听说你在码头上
earlier, but, uh, then I heard you on the dock.
我这顺风耳不巧听到了
Can't turn off my vamp hearing.
我不是想做偷窥打探之类的
I wasn't trying to spy or anything.
你的存在并不是个错误
You're not a mistake, okay?
这世界有你真好
The cosmos is lucky to have you.
兰登也是
So is Landon.
他会相通的
He'll figure that out.
你只需要做一个决定
CLARKE:  There's really only one thing  you have to decide.
你会帮我吗
Will you help me?
帮你释放马里之洼并毁灭世界吗
Help release Malivore and destroy the world?
他已经活了几个世纪了
He's been alive for centuries.
世界被毁灭了吗
Was the world destroyed?
还是他平衡了这世界
Or was it balanced
没有这些生物到处乱跑  这世界会更安全吗
and safer without all these creatures running around?
扪心自问  谁才是真正的坏人
Ask yourself-- who's the real bad guy here?
我们的父亲的存在是有意义的
Our father was designed for a purpose.
这是对他的设计  他也无力控制
It's his programming. He can't control that.
但是他吞下的所有的怪物
But all the monsters he swallowed
都还活在他体内
are still alive inside of him.
你的朋友让他们活着了吗
Did your friends keep any of them alive?
还是一旦有某种物种不受控制
Or did they just kill every creature
他们就杀了它
they couldn't control?
马里之洼伤不了
Malivore can't hurt
女巫  狼人和吸血鬼  记得吗
witches, werewolves, or vampires, remember?
你那些学校里的朋友
Your friends at the school--
他不会伤害他们的
they aren't in any danger from him.
但三元素会伤害他们
But they are in danger from Triad.
你知道这栋楼里发生了什么吗
You know what goes on in this building?
你知道他们在疯狂的科学实验室
What kind of secret experiments they run
做着什么样的秘密实验
in their mad scientist labs?
他们正在想办法把马里之洼变成武器
They're finding a way to turn the pit into a weapon.
用化学方法改变它
They're chemically altering it
这样就能用来对付不会受伤的物种
so it can be used against the protected species.
彻底终结超自然生物
Ending supernaturals once and for all.
你想救你的朋友吗
You want to save your friends?
那就阻止三元素
You have to stop Triad.
兰登
Landon,
不管他们在学校里是怎么教你的
no matter what they say at that school...
你和他们不一样
...you're not one of them.
你自己也清楚  对吧
And you know that, too, don't you?
我给你一个真正需要你的家庭
I'm offering you a family who actually wants you.
我们能帮父亲崛起
We can raise our father.
毁掉三元素
And we can destroy Triad.
你究竟怎么选
What's it gonna be?
这个
This one.
他桌子里只有这个东西
It was the only thing in his desk.
他是其中之一
He's one of them.
保安发现了个旧管道  他们一定是从那逃走的
Security found an old pipe that they must've escaped through.
地面上没有任何记录
There's no record of it on any ground plans.
没有找到他们的踪迹  但
They lost their trail, but...
他们找到了这个
they did find this.
* We could start from the top before we were hopeless... *
我知道他们要去那
I know where they're going.
召集队伍
Prep your team.
* We collide 'cause it's been quite a while... *
开始时  这世界是平衡的
You know, in the beginning,  there was balance.
我和卡罗琳开办学校的时候
You know, when Caroline and I opened the school,
这样做很有意义
it made sense.
但然后
Then it was...
只剩下我  然后
it was just me, and...
我以为我能坚强地
and I-I.. I thought I was strong enough
独自管理学校
to manage it alone.
但我真的
But I just...
犯了太多错误
made so many mistakes.
我想要是继续前行  就能摆脱这种感觉
I thought if I just kept moving, I could outrun them, you know?
但我却沉浸于此
But they caught up to me.
我大概是想说
I guess what I'm trying to say... is,
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
这所学校比你我都重要
You know, this school is bigger than you and me.
孩子们  他们需要领头人
And these kids-- they need leaders
能承认自己的错误的人
who can admit their mistakes.
所以我是来向你道歉的
And so I am here to say I'm sorry.
对不起  我吻了艾玛
I am sorry I kissed Emma.
对不起  我该及时向你坦白的
And I'm sorry I didn't talk to you sooner about it.
* Amen, amen*  Whoa... *
一直以来我都以为  我只是
You know, for a long time, I thought that I was only
因为我家人的遭遇才进的学校
at the school because of what happened to my family.
这样就能防止超自然生物
So that we could keep supernaturals
成长成杀人凶手
from growing up to be killers.
* Whoa * Amen, amen... *
但事实上
But the truth is...
* Amen, amen... *
我爱那些孩子们
I love those kids.
♪ Amen, amen... ♪
他们应该有机会和其他人一样
They deserve a chance at a normal life
过正常的生活
as much as anyone else.
这学校是他们最好的选择
The school is their best shot.
* Amen, amen * Whoa *
* Amen, amen...*
但我还要加薪
But I will need another raise.
*A... a... amen *
我要来
I'm coming.
你好呀  但是你不能来
Hello to you, too, uh, and, no, you're not.
上次你不带上我  就出大事了
Look, last time you did this without me, it was a disaster.
但我这次不是孤身一人犯险
Except I'm not gonna go alone this time.
我是和双胞胎姐妹  MG
I'm gonna draft the twins, MG,
凯勒布一起  在萨尔茨曼博士回来前出发
Kaleb. We're going before Dr. Saltzman comes back.
就像是个超级阵容大集合
It'll be like a Super Squad Assemble.
之类的  有这种说法吗
I don't know. Is that a thing?
不知道  等会问问MG
I don't know. I'll ask MG.
嗯  我自己去问他
Yeah, I'll ask him myself.
拉斐  萨尔茨曼博士告诉过我
Raf, Dr. Saltzman told me
副作用的事情  对不起  但你不能来
about the side effects. I'm sorry, but I can't let you come.
你现在感觉怎么样
How do you feel now?
就像大脑从中间裂开了一样
Like my brain's split down the middle.
我无法控制自己看到这些记忆碎片
I keep having these flashes like I can't control myself, and...
所以你不能来执行任务
That's why you're not coming on the mission.
为什么不早点告诉我
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
你知道原因
You know why.
拉斐
Raf...
霍普  我不知道在你身边该如何自处
I don't know how to be around you, Hope.
我不想有这种感觉
I don't want to feel this way,
于是深藏心里
so I push it down,
这只会让我大脑裂开的感觉更严重
and that just makes the split in my brain worse,
我也更难自持
which makes it harder to hide.
我唯一想对她倾诉的人
And the only person that I want to talk
却是我唯一不能与之倾诉的人
about it with is the only person I can't.
拉斐
Raf...
你是个好兄弟
you're a good brother.
但这次  你得把自己放在第一位
But for once, you need to put yourself first.
尽你所能让自己变得更好
Do what you need to get better.
要是事情真的每况愈下
If things get really bad...
就用这个
...use this.
说来话长了  但
It's a long story, but, um,
这是一位世交送的礼物
it was a gift from a family friend.
但它本质上就像一个反向的蓝晶石戒指
But it's essentially like a reverse kyanite ring.
使用时  你能任意变身
When you use it, you can turn yourself at will.
变身狼时  看待事情也简单多了
In your wolf mind, things are less complicated.
你懂的
You know that.
这能帮你更快恢复
It'll buy you time to heal.
唯一的问题是
Only catch is, um,
你自己没有办法变身回来
you can't turn yourself back, so,
要是你用了
if you do use it,
想变回自己的时候
all you have to do is come find me
你只要来找我
when you're ready to be yourself again.
我真的
I am
很高兴能认识你
really glad I know you...
霍普·迈克尔森
Hope Mikaelson.
快
Now,
出发吧
go.
把咱兄弟救回来
Go save our boy.
不要让任何事情阻止你
And don't let anything  stop you.
上  快走
Move, move!
■
人人视频APP
在线观看美剧
离线高清缓存
更有海量高清电影
扫码即刻下载
特别推荐
■
各大应用市场均可下载
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）